[
    {
        "campaignDetail": {
            "id": 1,
            "name": "Karmic OSLO: The Bike of the Future is Here!",
            "fund_raiser_id": 20,
            "short_pitch": "A modern electric bicycle that shrinks your city and reduces your footprint.",
            "address": "DesMoines",
            "city": "DesMoines",
            "fund_required": 10000,
            "description": "Hey Kickstarter! We are Karmic, and we build modern electric bicycles. \nWe’re launching our third campaign for the new Karmic OSLO. Since we brought you the Koben, the market has been inundated with hundreds, if not thousands, of electric bikes. Most of them start with a standard bike frame, adding a battery and a motor. We should know, we did that 4 years ago. But shouldn’t technology have taken us further by now? Shouldn’t we be riding the future already? \nIn spite of everything out there, we believe the best electric bike had yet to be built. \nSo we built it.\nWe’ve spent the last few years engineering a new kind of electric bike. We’ve reimagined movement from the ground up to bring you something unlike anything you’ve ever seen before. Presenting the OSLO.\n",
            "is_approved": true,
            "equity_stake": 2,
            "created_time": null,
            "start_date": null,
            "end_date": null,
            "capitalRaisedIndividually" : 50,
            "capitalRaisedInFunds" :40
    
        },
        "campaignFandQs": [
            {
                "question": "Why us?",
                "answer": "Because of me"
            },
            {
                "question": "How was this idea?",
                "answer": "Because of you"
            }
        ],
        "campaignTeams": [
            {
                "name": "Avinash Kumar",
                "profile": "CFO",
                "email_id": "avinash@email.com"
            }
        ],
        "campaignFinancialReports": [
            {
                "year": 2019,
                "value": 25000,
                "report": "PROFIT"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "campaignDetail": {
            "id": 2,
            "name": "Karmic OSLO: The Bike of the Future is Here!",
            "fund_raiser_id": 20,
            "short_pitch": "A modern electric bicycle that shrinks your city and reduces your footprint.",
            "address": "DesMoines",
            "city": "DesMoines",
            "fund_required": 10000,
            "description": "Hey Kickstarter! We are Karmic, and we build modern electric bicycles. \nWe’re launching our third campaign for the new Karmic OSLO. Since we brought you the Koben, the market has been inundated with hundreds, if not thousands, of electric bikes. Most of them start with a standard bike frame, adding a battery and a motor. We should know, we did that 4 years ago. But shouldn’t technology have taken us further by now? Shouldn’t we be riding the future already? \nIn spite of everything out there, we believe the best electric bike had yet to be built. \nSo we built it.\nWe’ve spent the last few years engineering a new kind of electric bike. We’ve reimagined movement from the ground up to bring you something unlike anything you’ve ever seen before. Presenting the OSLO.\n",
            "is_approved": true,
            "equity_stake": 2,
            "created_time": null,
            "start_date": null,
            "end_date": null,
            "capitalRaisedIndividually" : 50,
            "capitalRaisedInFunds" :40
    
        },
        "campaignFandQs": [
            {
                "question": "Why us?",
                "answer": "Because of me"
            },
            {
                "question": "How was this idea?",
                "answer": "Because of you"
            }
        ],
        "campaignTeams": [
            {
                "name": "Avinash Kumar",
                "profile": "CFO",
                "email_id": "avinash@email.com"
            }
        ],
        "campaignFinancialReports": [
            {
                "year": 2019,
                "value": 25000,
                "report": "PROFIT"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "campaignDetail": {
            "id": 3,
            "name": "Karmic OSLO: The Bike of the Future is Here!",
            "fund_raiser_id": 20,
            "short_pitch": "A modern electric bicycle that shrinks your city and reduces your footprint.",
            "address": "DesMoines",
            "city": "DesMoines",
            "fund_required": 10000,
            "description": "Hey Kickstarter! We are Karmic, and we build modern electric bicycles. \nWe’re launching our third campaign for the new Karmic OSLO. Since we brought you the Koben, the market has been inundated with hundreds, if not thousands, of electric bikes. Most of them start with a standard bike frame, adding a battery and a motor. We should know, we did that 4 years ago. But shouldn’t technology have taken us further by now? Shouldn’t we be riding the future already? \nIn spite of everything out there, we believe the best electric bike had yet to be built. \nSo we built it.\nWe’ve spent the last few years engineering a new kind of electric bike. We’ve reimagined movement from the ground up to bring you something unlike anything you’ve ever seen before. Presenting the OSLO.\n",
            "is_approved": true,
            "equity_stake": 2,
            "created_time": null,
            "start_date": null,
            "end_date": null,
            "capitalRaisedIndividually" : 50,
            "capitalRaisedInFunds" :40
    
        },
        "campaignFandQs": [
            {
                "question": "Why us?",
                "answer": "Because of me"
            },
            {
                "question": "How was this idea?",
                "answer": "Because of you"
            }
        ],
        "campaignTeams": [
            {
                "name": "Avinash Kumar",
                "profile": "CFO",
                "email_id": "avinash@email.com"
            }
        ],
        "campaignFinancialReports": [
            {
                "year": 2019,
                "value": 25000,
                "report": "PROFIT"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "campaignDetail": {
            "id": 4,
            "name": "Karmic OSLO: The Bike of the Future is Here!",
            "fund_raiser_id": 20,
            "short_pitch": "A modern electric bicycle that shrinks your city and reduces your footprint.",
            "address": "DesMoines",
            "city": "DesMoines",
            "fund_required": 10000,
            "description": "Hey Kickstarter! We are Karmic, and we build modern electric bicycles. \nWe’re launching our third campaign for the new Karmic OSLO. Since we brought you the Koben, the market has been inundated with hundreds, if not thousands, of electric bikes. Most of them start with a standard bike frame, adding a battery and a motor. We should know, we did that 4 years ago. But shouldn’t technology have taken us further by now? Shouldn’t we be riding the future already? \nIn spite of everything out there, we believe the best electric bike had yet to be built. \nSo we built it.\nWe’ve spent the last few years engineering a new kind of electric bike. We’ve reimagined movement from the ground up to bring you something unlike anything you’ve ever seen before. Presenting the OSLO.\n",
            "is_approved": true,
            "equity_stake": 2,
            "created_time": null,
            "start_date": null,
            "end_date": null,
            "capitalRaisedIndividually" : 50,
            "capitalRaisedInFunds" :40
    
        },
        "campaignFandQs": [
            {
                "question": "Why us?",
                "answer": "Because of me"
            },
            {
                "question": "How was this idea?",
                "answer": "Because of you"
            }
        ],
        "campaignTeams": [
            {
                "name": "Avinash Kumar",
                "profile": "CFO",
                "email_id": "avinash@email.com"
            }
        ],
        "campaignFinancialReports": [
            {
                "year": 2019,
                "value": 25000,
                "report": "PROFIT"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "campaignDetail": {
            "id": 5,
            "name": "Karmic OSLO: The Bike of the Future is Here!",
            "fund_raiser_id": 20,
            "short_pitch": "A modern electric bicycle that shrinks your city and reduces your footprint.",
            "address": "DesMoines",
            "city": "DesMoines",
            "fund_required": 10000,
            "description": "Hey Kickstarter! We are Karmic, and we build modern electric bicycles. \nWe’re launching our third campaign for the new Karmic OSLO. Since we brought you the Koben, the market has been inundated with hundreds, if not thousands, of electric bikes. Most of them start with a standard bike frame, adding a battery and a motor. We should know, we did that 4 years ago. But shouldn’t technology have taken us further by now? Shouldn’t we be riding the future already? \nIn spite of everything out there, we believe the best electric bike had yet to be built. \nSo we built it.\nWe’ve spent the last few years engineering a new kind of electric bike. We’ve reimagined movement from the ground up to bring you something unlike anything you’ve ever seen before. Presenting the OSLO.\n",
            "is_approved": true,
            "equity_stake": 2,
            "created_time": null,
            "start_date": null,
            "end_date": null,
            "capitalRaisedIndividually" : 50,
            "capitalRaisedInFunds" :40
    
        },
        "campaignFandQs": [
            {
                "question": "Why us?",
                "answer": "Because of me"
            },
            {
                "question": "How was this idea?",
                "answer": "Because of you"
            }
        ],
        "campaignTeams": [
            {
                "name": "Avinash Kumar",
                "profile": "CFO",
                "email_id": "avinash@email.com"
            }
        ],
        "campaignFinancialReports": [
            {
                "year": 2019,
                "value": 25000,
                "report": "PROFIT"
            }
        ]
    }
]